trusted by the people of Hong Kong
sunlife Hong Kong is the first Insurance
of Hong Kong sunlife ESG focused savings
products standing at the Forefront of
the market the product focuses on
environmental social and governance
investing in assets with high ESG
ratings together with our unique ESG
plus research and framework we're able
to deliver long-term stable return for
clients the brand new Sunjoy is one of
our Flagship savings products that
focuses on the ESG concept it offers
potential long-term wealth growth and
the flexibility to withdraw projected
policy value as needed while also
serving as a comprehensive Legacy
solution tool one move two
gains taking Samy as an example she
purchased Sunjoy 5 years ago and now
withdraws money from the policy annually
even though her daughter is studying in
a university in the UK she can visit her
daughter regularly apart from education
living and medical expenses the
withdrawals can also be used to afford
family expenses for her parents it can
even be used for investing in person
person startups further studies and so
on whether the payment period is 2 pay
or 5 pay it offers potential long-term
wealth growth and flexibility of
withdrawals taking five pay as an
example the whole policy only needs 5
years of contribution client can choose
to withdraw the policy value of policy
at any time or withdraw cash value
annually equal to 5% of the total
premiums after the end of the fifth
policy year realizing great financial
flexibility in Samy's case the annual
premium was 00,000
the total premiums paid over 5 years was
$500,000 she decided to withdraw cash
value equal to 5% of the total premiums
paid from the policy in the fifth policy
year that is
$225,000 perom after 20 years of
withdrawals the accumulated withdrawal
amount has reached 100% of the total
premiums paid as Sammy reaches age 85
the total policy value that is the
accumulated withdrawal amount of cash
value plus the remaining total cash
value has exceeded 3 million us
which is equivalent to 62% of the total
premiums paid how does the plan help in
case of emergency the plan offers the
first in Market free accidental caring
plus benefit if the insured is unable to
perform at least three of the activities
of daily living due to accident we will
provide you with additional care and
financial
support moreover assuming Samy passed
away at age 75 the remaining amount in
policy approximated $1.3 million would
be paid as death benefit paying under
six different types of death benefit
settlement options to each beneficiary
to be passed on to her loved ones
following her
wishes the plan not only offers savings
solution but also Legacy planning
firstly client can pass on the policy
via changing the insured to their
children or even children's Next
Generation until the insured reaches the
age of 120 secondly the policy owner can
split the notional amount of a policy
into as many policies with different
percentages as he or she wants and then
pass on the split policies to several
family members the policy split option
provides the flexibility to change the
insured or the policy owner so that
everyone can receive protection Sunjoy
is not only flexible in terms of
withdrawal but the cash value of the
revisionary bonus is also guaranteed
once it is declared with a wide range of
possibilities Sunjoy is the most
comprehensive wealth growth tool in the
market that helps you fulfill your life
goals as well as take care of your loved
ones and on top of that passing your
wealth to the next Generations
contact us to get ready for the
future